<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Doomkeeper.com]]></title>
  <link href="http://codeisart.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://codeisart.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-27T22:10:49-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://codeisart.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Jimmy Smith]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Converted Blog to Octopress]]></title>
    <link href="http://codeisart.github.io/blog/2014/04/19/converted-blog-to-octopress/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-19T23:05:17-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://codeisart.github.io/blog/2014/04/19/converted-blog-to-octopress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2><img src="http://codeisart.github.io/images/octopress.png" title="Octopress" alt="Octopress Rocks" /></h2>

<p>Ok quick update to say that I&rsquo;ve finally <em>switched</em> over the blog to <a href="http://octopress.org">Octopress</a>. It&rsquo;s been a long time coming because I&rsquo;ve been busy with lots of things, blah, blah, blah.</p>

<ol>
<li>Buying a house.</li>
<li>Becoming Fulltime at Microsoft BlackTusk</li>
<li>Doing a bunch of travelling.</li>
</ol>


<h2>Why?</h2>

<p>One of the <em>big</em> reasons being that I&rsquo;ve been somewhat nagged, (although <a href="http://buffered.io">he&rsquo;ll</a> never admit to it), that I should move to a statically hosted site. All the cool kids are doing it so why not? Well, mainly procratistation and lack significant motivation. Well a reather <em>large</em> motivator came in the form of a site I had to host for a friends wedding.</p>

<p>I discovered the somewhat unglamerous side of things when a site I hosted was hacked and started injecting malware to people. PHP seemed to be a inherently insecure framework; a metaphorical swiss cheese of vulnerabilities that was near impossible to stay on top off. As a adminstrator I could never really sleep well at night knowing that it was essentially a shooting gallery for wanna be hackers (script kiddies). The logs very literally full of SQL injection attempts and another Wordpress/PHP style attacks.</p>

<h2>Ungreatful bastard</h2>

<p>You know the Best Man was actually going to mention me in his speech, saying he&rsquo;d lost his &ldquo;entire computer to a virus&rdquo;. Yeah right Jackass. Although I was never there to hear it, thankfully. We haven&rsquo;t spoken since. So clearly PHP is great way of ridding yourself of terrible friends. Lol.</p>

<p>So this is my attempt something to do something a little different. I&rsquo;m also going to try and reduce my hostings cost as <a href="http://aws.amazon.com/">Amazon</a> and <a href="http://vpslink.com/">VpsLink</a> are burning a hole in my pocket. House buying will do that I guess.</p>

<p>I quite like the markdown syntax. If you&rsquo;ve never seen it you should <a href="https://github.com/adam-p/markdown-here/wiki/Markdown-Cheatsheet">check it out</a>. I kind of wish it has existed years ago when I had to churn out a tone of web pages for university.</p>

<p>I did attempt to convert my old blog over to Octopress, but the caching plugin that I had installed, seemed to make nearly impossible to reach the admin console. Joy. So maybe it&rsquo;s a blessing diguise, I&rsquo;ll start a fresh. Yes I know I can dump it out from the SQL instance, but you know I don&rsquo;t really care.</p>

<p>Anyways, I suppose I&rsquo;ll point <a href="http://doomkeeper.com/blog">Doomkeeper.com</a> at this site when I&rsquo;m done here.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
